And that's why, no matter what Mommy says..
而那就是为什么不管妈咪说什么…
we really were on a break. Yes, we were.
我们都真的暂时分手了 是的，没错…
Yes, we were. Come here, gorgeous.
是的，没错 来吧，漂亮宝贝
Look at you. You are the cutest little baby ever.
瞧瞧你 你是史上最可爱的小婴儿了
You're just a little-bitty baby, you know that? But you've got..
你只是个小不丁点婴儿 你知道吗？但是你拥有…
You've got big, beautiful eyes.
你拥有大大漂亮的双眼
Yes, you do. And a.. And a big, round belly.
是的，你有，还有… 还有大大圆圆的肚肚
Big baby butt.
大大的婴儿屁屁
I like big butts.
我喜欢大屁屁
Oh, my God, Emma. You're laughing.
喔，天啊，艾犸你在笑
Oh, my God. You've never done that before, have you?
喔，我的天，你从没有这样过，对吗？
You've never done that before. Daddy made you laugh, huh?
你从来没有这样过 爹地逗你笑了，对吧？
Well, Daddy and Sir Mix-A-Lot.
嗯，是爹地还有混音老爹
What? What? You wanna hear some more?
什么？什么？ 你还想听更多是吗？
I'm a terrible father.
我真是个糟糕的父亲
The One With Rosss Inappropriate Song
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
- What do you know about investments? - How come?
-你们懂得投资吗？ -怎么了？
I'm starting to make good money on the show, and I should do something with it.
我的演出开始让我赚到一些钱了 所以我想我应该好好利用那些钱
- What do you do with your money now? - It's taped to the back of my toilet tank.
-那你现在是把钱放在哪里呢？ -藏在我家马桶水箱后面
I didn't say that. It's in a bank guarded by robots.
我没有那样说 是放在银行由机器人看守着
- Do you have any ideas? - A guy at work got me excited..
-你有什么想法吗？ -有个同事的提议让我觉得很兴奋…
about going in on an emu farm. That'd be kind of cool, huh?
是关于投资鸸鸟农场 很酷吧？
Pitching in on the weekends, helping to plant the emus.
在周末的时候过去帮忙 帮助种植鸸鸟
Joe, emus are birds. You raise them for meat.
乔伊，鸸鸟是鸟类 是养来当食物的
Yeah. Right!
嗯，是喔！
People eat birds. Bird meat.
人类会吃小鸟，小鸟肉
Do they just fly into your mouth? Or you go in a restaurant and say:
他们是直接飞进你的嘴里吗？ 还是你可以到餐厅说：
"Excuse me, I'll have a bucket of fried bird."
“不好意思，我要点一份炸鸟”
Or maybe just a wing. Or a..
或是一个翅膀，或是…
You should consider something a little less risky.
你应该考虑比较低风险性的投资
I think real estate is your best investment.
我认为房地产会是最好的投资
The Fed just lowered the rates, and the interest on your mortgage is deductible.
联邦储备银行才刚降息 而且房贷的利率也可以扣减所得税额
That's right. I know some stuff.
没错，我懂投资
Real estate, huh?
房地产，是吗？
And you know who's selling a great apartment? Richard!
你知道谁要卖一间 很棒的公寓吗？李察！
And you know whose knowledge of her ex-boyfriend is shocking? Monica!
你知道谁对她前男朋友的熟悉度 很吓人吗？摩妮卡！
- My dad told me. They play golf together. - Well, maybe I'll join them sometime.
-我爸告诉我的，他们一起打高尔夫球 -那么或许我应该加入他们
I just hope the club doesn't slip out of my hand..
我只希望球杆不要滑出我的手…
and beat the mustache off his face.
然后把他的八字胡从他脸上打掉
And then the doctor said Emma has doubled her birth weight..
然后医生说艾犸的体重 已经是出生时的一倍了…
she is in the 90th percentile and she's gonna start eating solid foods soon.
她比百分之九十的婴儿快 很快就可以吃固体食物了
- That's great! - I know!
-太棒了！ -我知道！
- What did we used to talk about? - No idea.
-我们以前都在谈什么呢？ -不知道
Hi! You have to help me pick a dress. I'm meeting Mike's parents tonight.
嗨！你们要帮我选衣服 我今晚要跟麦克的父母见面
Wow, the boyfriend's parents. That's a big step.
哇，男朋友的父母亲，真是一大步
- Really? That hadn't occurred to me. - They'll love you. Just be yourself.
-真的吗？我倒是没有这样想过 -他们会喜欢你的，自然随性就好
They live on the Upper East Side on Park Avenue.
他们住在上东区的公园大道
Yeah, she can't be herself.
那她就不能自然随性了
Okay, so, all right, which dress?
好了，那么，哪一件呢？
- You can say neither. - Oh, God. Neither.
-你们可以说都不好 -喔，天啊，都不好
You can say it nicely.
你们大可以委婉一点说
I'm sorry. We'll take you shopping. It'll be fine.
我很抱歉，我们会带你去买衣服 没事的
You are in such good hands, and I am so good with meeting parents.
我会照顾你的 我很会搞跟父母亲见面这种事
With the father, you wanna flirt a little, but not in a gross way.
面对他父亲，稍微打情骂俏一下 但是不要太过火
Just kind of like, "Mr. Pinzer, I can see where Wallace gets his good looks."
有像是“品瑟先生，我现在终于知道 华勒斯帅气的长相是遗传谁的了”
- You went out with Wallace Pinzer? - He took the SATs for me.
-你跟华勒斯品瑟交往过？ -他代替我考联考
- I knew you didn't get a 1400! - Yeah, well, duh! I mean..
-我就知道你没有考过高标！ -是啊，哈！我们说的是我耶…
So now, what about with Mike's mom?
那麦克的妈怎么办呢？
Well, with the mother, just constantly tell her how amazing her son is.
至于他母亲，只要不断的告诉她 她儿子有多棒就行了
Take it from me. Moms love me. Ross' mom one time actually said..
举我为例，母亲们都很喜欢我 罗斯的妈有一次甚至还说…
I am like the daughter that she never had.
我就像是那个她从未有过的女儿
- She said what? - She's like the daughter she never had.
-她说什么？ -她就像是那个她从未有过的女儿
Listen.
听着
I just got Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents.
我才帮菲比打扮好让她去见麦克的父母
She's so nervous. It's so sweet.
她好紧张，真是太感人了
Guess what. I made Emma laugh today.
猜猜怎么了，我今天逗艾犸笑了
You what? And I missed it..
你什么？而我竟然错过…
because I was giving a makeover to that stupid hippie?!
都是因为要帮那 愚蠢的嬉皮改变造型？
Yeah, and it was like a real little person laugh too.
是啊，而且就像是小大人的笑喔！
It was like:
就像是…
Only not creepy.
只不过不像这样吓人
- What did you do to make her laugh? - I..
-你做了什么逗她笑？ -我…
Well, I sang. Actually..
嗯，我唱了歌 其实…
I rapped..
是饶舌歌…
"Baby Got Back."
“宝贝，你的马达真正”
You what?
你什么？
You sang to our baby daughter..
你对着我们的宝贝女儿唱…
a song about a guy who likes to have sex..
一首关于男人想要跟巨大屁股女人…
with women with giant asses?
上床的歌？
You know what, if you think about it..
你知道吗？如果你仔细想想…
it actually promotes a healthy body image..
它事实上是在提倡健康的身体观念…
because even big butts..
因为即使是大屁股…
or "juicy doubles" are..
或是“可口多汁的双颊”都是…
Please don't take her away from me.
请不要把她从我身边带走
Hi, come on in. I'm Catherine, the listing agent.
嗨，请进 我是凯瑟琳，仲介商
Hi, I'm Joey. This is Chandler.
嗨，我是乔伊，这是钱德
So how come Richard's selling the place? Went bankrupt?
为什么李察要卖掉这地方呢？ 破产了吗？
Medical malpractice? Choked on his own mustache?
医疗误诊？被自己的胡子噎死吗？
He's buying a much bigger place. It's got a great view of Central Park..
他要买一间更大的公寓 景观很棒，可以看到中央公园…
That's enough out of you.
你说够了！
Is there anything we should know about the place?
这地方有什么我们应该要知道的吗？
All the appliances are included. There's a lot of light, a new kitchen.
电器用品全部都包含 光线充足，还有新的厨房
I think you guys would be very happy here.
我想你们俩住在这里一定会很快乐
No, we're not together. We're definitely not a couple.
不，我们没有在一起 我们绝对不是一对
- Okay. Sorry. - That's all right.
-好的，抱歉 -没关系
Wow, you seemed pretty insulted by that.
哇，你看起来好像是被侮辱了一样
What, I'm not good enough for you?
是怎样？我配不上你吗？
We are not gonna have this conversation again.
我们不要再讨论这个问题了
Look at this place. Why am I so intimidated by this guy?
瞧瞧这地方 我为什么备受这家伙的威胁呢？
Pretentious art. This huge, macho couch.
矫情的艺术品，这张大又阳刚的沙发
When we know all he does is sit around..
我们知道他只会坐在那边…
crying about losing Monica to a real man.
哭泣着为什么摩妮卡会离开他 而投入一个真正男人的怀抱
- You don't think he's here, do you? - I don't know.
-他应该不在这里吧，对吗？ -我不知道
It's a nice place, but I gotta say, I don't know if I see myself living here.
这是个好地方，但是我必须要说 我不知道我能不能住得习惯
Well, let me see.
嗯，让我们来试试看
Yeah, I can see it.
是的，我可以住得习惯
Look at these videos. I mean, who does he think he is?
瞧瞧这些录影带 他以为他是谁啊？
Magnum Force, Dirty Harry, Cool Hand Luke.
《辣手神探追魂枪》、《紧急追捕令》 《铁窗喋血》
- Oh, my God. - What?
-喔，我的天 -怎么了？
There's a tape here with Monica's name on it.
有一卷带子上面有摩妮卡的名字
A tape with a girl's name on it. It's probably a sex tape.
有一卷带子上面有女生的名字 可能是性爱绿影带
Wait a minute.
等一下
This says "Monica."
上面写着“摩妮卡”…
And this is Richard's apartment.
而且这里是李察的公寓
Get there faster!
快点想！
Wow. You look..
哇，你看起来…
like my mom.
真像我妈
I'm wearing pantyhose.
我有穿丝袜
- Great! Come on in. - Okay.
-太棒了！请进 -好的
Thank you.
谢谢
- Oh, my God. You're rich. - No, my parents are rich.
-喔，我的天，你真有钱 -不，是我父母亲有钱
Well, so? They gotta die someday. Hello!
喔，那又如何呢？他们有天也会死的 哈！
Mom, Dad, this is Phoebe.
爸妈，这是菲比
Phoebe, these are my parents, Theodore and Bitsy.
菲比，他们是我父母 希尔多跟贝西
Theodore, Bitsy..
希尔多，贝西…
what a delight.
很高兴能与你们见面
- It's so nice to finally meet you. - And you.
-终于见到你真是太高兴了 -我也是
Your home is lovely.
你们家真是美好
Thank you. I'll give you a tour later. It's actually three floors.
谢谢，等一下我可以带你参观 这里其实有三层楼
Holy crap!
妈妈咪啊！
Why don't you come meet our friends.
过来认识我们的朋友吧！
Try and stop me.
试试挡我看看
- What are you doing? - Trying to get your parents to like me.
-你在做什么呢？ -试着让你父母亲喜欢我
I'm sure they will, but you don't have to do this.
我相信他们会的，但是你不用这样假
I want them to get to know Phoebe, not "Phoebe."
我要他们认识菲比，不是“妃妣”
It is fun, though, isn't it?
不过很好玩，不是吗？
- You've got it. - All right.
-知道了 -好了
It's hard to stop.
很难停止
Well, come on.
好了，来吧
Phoebe, these are our friends Tom and Sue Engel.
菲比，这是我们的朋友 汤姆跟苏安格
Phoebe, come sit. Tell us a little bit about yourself.
菲比，来坐下 跟我们介绍一下你自己
- So where are you from? - Okay.
-你是哪里人呢？ -好的
Well, all right. Originally, I'm from upstate..
嗯，好的，我本来是上州人…
but then my mom killed herself, and my stepdad went to prison.
但是后来我妈自杀，然后继父去坐牢
So I moved to the city, where I lived in a burned-out Buick LeSabre for a while.
所以我就搬到市中心 住在一辆火烧车里一阵子
Which was okay. That was okay.
那倒是没关系，还好啦
Until I got hepatitis, you know..
直到我染上肝炎，你知道的…
because this pimp spit in my mouth and..
因为有个坏蛋吐口水到我嘴里然后…
But I got over it.
但是我已经好了
And, anyway, now I'm a freelance massage therapist..
然后，反正现在我是 自由按摩治疗师…
which isn't always steady money, but at least I don't pay taxes.
赚的钱不是很稳固，但至少不用缴税
So where does everyone summer?
那大家都到哪度暑假呢？
I'm not gonna watch it. I don't need to watch it.
我不会看的，我不需要看
I mean, what good could possibly come from watching it?
我是说，看了又有什么好处呢？
Well, we know I'm gonna watch it.
嗯，我们知道我还是要看
- Hey, dude, what's up? - Don't judge me! I'm only human!
-嘿，兄弟，怎么了？ -别审判我！我只不过是个普通人！
Did you take that tape?
你拿走那卷带子吗？
I had to! Imagine you were married and you found a tape of your wife..
我必须要！假设你结婚了 然后你发现一卷你老婆带子…
in another guy's apartment. Wouldn't you need to know what was on it?
在另一个男人的公寓里 你难道不想知道里面是什么吗？
I don't know. Who am I married to?
我不知道，我跟谁结婚呢？
Some girl.
某个女孩子
She hot?
她辣吗？
How did she get me to settle down?
她是怎么让我定下来的？
All right, I'm gonna watch it.
好了，我要看
I mean, it's probably not even what I think it is.
我是说，或许根本不是我想的那样
Even if it is, it can't possibly be as bad as what I'm picturing in my head.
即使是，或许也不像我在脑海中 想像的情景那样糟糕
Can it?
会吗？
In my experience, if a girl says yes to being taped..
依据我的经验 如果女生答应可以录下来…
she doesn't say no to much else, I'll tell you.
其它的也就都不会拒绝了 我跟你说
- Then you have to watch it for me. - What?
-那你先帮我看 -什么？
Just for a few seconds so I can know what it is. Please?
几秒钟就好，让我知道那是什么，拜托
All right, fine. But if I enjoy this, you have only yourself to blame!
好啦，可以，但是万一我很乐在其中 你就只能怪你自己！
- Why am I hearing cheering? - It's okay. It's just a football game.
-为什么我听到欢呼声？ -没关系，是足球赛
- It's just football? - You were all worried for nothing.
-只是足球赛？ -你担心是多余的
It's football! It's just football!
是足球！只是足球！
This is great! This is the first time I've ever enjoyed football!
太棒了！这是我第一次真正喜欢足球！
I think it may be customary to get a beer.
我想这时候喝啤酒很对味
What the..?
搞什么…？
- What are you doing? - You don't wanna see what I just saw!
-你在做什么？ -你不想要看到我刚看到的东西！
What are you guys doing?
你们在做什么？
Oh, my God! Is that Richard?
喔，我的天！那是李察吗？
- Oh, God, this is not going well. - No, you're doing fine. Really.
-喔，天啊，真是进行的不顺利 -不，你做的很好，真的
- Why don't you go talk to my dad. - Okay, okay, okay.
-你何不去找我爸聊聊 -好，好的，好的
- Still sure about me being myself? - Absolutely.
-还确定要我做我自己吗？ -当然
Though maybe just a little less "pimp spit."
或许少说一些“坏蛋吐口水”的事
So, Theodore, I can see where Mike gets his good looks from.
希尔多，我现在知道麦克的帅气外表 是遗传自谁的了
Well..
嗯…
- You must work out all the time. - Not all the time. I do the best I can.
-你一定经常做运动 -不是很常，不过我尽量
Yeah, I bet. Look out!
是啊，我想也是，看招！
- Oh, my God. Are you okay? - I recently had surgery.
-喔，我的天，你还好吗？ -我最近刚动完手术
- I'm so sorry. - No, I'll be fine.
-我很抱歉 -没关系，我没事
- I just should check the stitches. - I really am sorry.
-我只是应该要去检查一下伤口 -我真的很抱歉
How could you know? Why wouldn't you punch me in the stomach?
你怎么会知道呢？ 为什么你不会打我肚子呢？
Did you just hit my dad?
你刚刚是不是打了我爸？
Yes. I'm sorry. I've never met a boyfriend's parents before.
是的，我很抱歉 我从来没有见过男朋友的父母亲
But, I mean, you have met humans before, right?
但是，你总该有见过人，对吗？
Why don't you go talk to my mom.
你何不去找我妈聊聊
Okay, yeah, your mom. She looks nice. I can talk to her.
好的，你妈，她看起来很和善 我可以跟她聊的
You do that, and I'm gonna go check my dad for signs of internal bleeding.
你去聊吧！ 我要去看看我爸是不是有内出血的现象
Bitsy? Listen, I wanted to thank you again for having me here tonight.
贝西，我想要再次谢谢你 邀请我今晚过来
Well, not at all.
喔，不用客气
Also, I just want you to know what a wonderful man your son is.
还有，我只想让你知道 你儿子是个很棒的男人
- Thank you. I think so too. - It's a testament to how he was raised.
-谢谢，我也这么认为 -一切都是他受了良好的家庭教育
Especially to you, because he's very respectful of women.
尤其是你的功劳 因为他十分尊重女性
- Is he really? - He is so considerate of my feelings.
-他真的吗？ -他非常体贴我的感受
You know, I think you'd also like to know that he is a very gentle lover.
我认为你也会想知道 他是个非常温柔的爱人
Excuse me?
什么？
No, don't get me wrong. No, not in like a sissy way.
不，别误会我 不，不是那种娘娘腔的样子
When he gets going..
当他疯起来的时候…
he can rattle a headboard like a sailor on leave.
他可是像休假的船员一样神勇
That's.. my boy.
那就是…我儿子
Awesome.
酷毙了
Okay, please laugh for Mommy. Please?
好了，帮妈咪笑一笑 拜托
Please laugh for Mommy.
请为妈咪笑一个
Not funny, huh?
不好笑，对吧？
Well, so is it..
嗯，所以是不是…
only offensive novelty rap?
只有低级好玩的饶舌歌才行呢？
Or maybe just, you know, rap in general. Because Mommy can rap.
或是或许只要是饶舌歌都行 因为妈咪会饶舌喔
I can't rap.
我不会饶舌
All right, sweetheart. This is only because I love you so much.
好了，亲爱的，这只是因为我太爱你了
And I know that you're not gonna tell anybody.
而且我知道你不会告诉别人
Emma, you're laughing! You are!
艾犸，你在笑！你笑了！
You really do like big butts, don't you?
你真的很喜欢大屁股，对不对？
You beautiful little weirdo.
你这个漂亮的小怪蛋
You missed it! She was laughing!
你错过了！她刚刚在笑！
It was amazing.
真是不可思议
It was amazing. It was the most beautiful, beautiful sound.
是很不可思议，那就像是最美妙的声音
I know, isn't it? What'd you do to get her to laugh?
我知道，可不是吗？ 你做了什么逗她笑？
You know, I just.. A couple of things I tried. Different..
你知道的，我只不过… 试了一些东西，不同的…
Just sang a little "The Itsy-Bitsy Spider."
只是唱了一点“痒痒小蜘蛛”
You sang "Baby Got Back, " didn't you?
你唱了“宝贝，你的马达真正” 对不对？
Nothing else worked! That girl is all about the ass!
其它的方法都没有用！ 这女孩就是喜欢屁屁！
And then it goes back to the chorus.
然后再回到主旋律
Resolve. And that's the end of the song.
然后那就是歌曲的结尾
I realize you hadn't asked to hear it..
我知道你们没有要我唱…
but no one had spoken in 17 minutes.
但是已经有十七分钟没有人说话了
Phoebe writes lots of songs. What was that one you sang the other night?
菲比创作了许多歌曲 你那天晚上唱的歌是什么呢？
"Pervert Parade"?
《变态游行》吗？
- "Ode to a Pubic Hair"? - Stop.
-《阴毛颂》吗？ -停止
Oh, God. Is that veal?
喔，天啊，这是小牛肉吗？
Mom, I thought I told you, Phoebe's a vegetarian.
妈，我以为我跟你说过菲比是素食者
No, that's okay. That's okay. I mean, I am a vegetarian..
不，没关系，没关系 我是说，我是素食者…
except for veal. Yeah. No. Veal I love.
不过我吃小牛肉 是的，我爱吃小牛肉
- Phoebe, you don't have to eat that. - Any baby animals. Kittens, fish babies.
-菲比，你可以不用吃的 -我喜欢任何小动物食物，小猫，小鱼
But, you know, especially veal.
但是，尤其喜欢小牛肉
You know, and this nice vein of fat running through it.
这上面还有带一点很棒的肥肉
Yummy.
好吃
So..
那…
what do you think?
你们觉得如何呢？
So you stole that tape from Richard's apartment?
所以你从李察的公寓偷了这卷带子？
Listen to the judgment from the porn star!
听听这三级片脱星在批评我！
That tape was never meant to be seen by..
那带子本来就不是要让…
Joey, I would feel more comfortable if this conversation were in private.
乔伊，我希望可以私下谈论这件事
Monica, look, I don't think you and I have any secrets anymore.
摩妮卡，听着，我不认为 你我之间有存在任何秘密了
Not ready to joke about it yet? See you later.
还没有准备好可以开玩笑吗？待会见
Why in the world would you take this tape? And why would you watch it?
你为什么要拿这卷带子呢？ 而且为什么要看呢？
Because that's who I am. Okay?
因为我就是这样的人，好吗？
I'm sure a man like Richard could see a tape like that and not be bothered.
我相信像李察那样的男人可以 看这样的带子而且不会被说教
It'd just be another saucy anecdote..
这只不过是个黄色的小插曲…
for him to share at his men's club over brandy and mustaches.
让他可以在他的男性俱乐部里 边喝着白兰地摸着胡子和兄弟们分享
Is all of this about you not being able to grow a mustache?
这一切跟你没有办法长胡子有关吗？
This is about you and Richard. He's clearly not over you.
这跟你还有李察有关 很明显地他还没有忘记你
He keeps a tape so he can look at it whenever he wants.
他保留这带子让他可以 在任何想的时候就看
Isn't that sad? Can't you see how pathetic that is?
那不是很悲惨吗？ 你看不出来这是多可悲的事吗？
Don't be jealous. You should feel bad for him.
别吃醋了，你应该为他感到可怜
Yeah, well, poor Richard, he..
是啊，可怜的李察，他…
I can grow a mustache.
我可以长胡子的
This is not our problem. We have each other. That's all that matters.
这不是我们的问题，我们拥有彼此 这是最重要的
But I just keep picturing you rolling around with him, with your..
但是我就是忘不了你滚在他身边 穿着你的…
cowboy boots in the air.
牛仔靴子在空中晃来晃去
Cowboy boots? I've never worn cowboy boots in my whole life.
牛仔靴子？我这辈子 从没有穿过牛仔靴子
Good, good. Play more because I wanna see how it ends.
很好，非常好，再多放一点 因为我想看结局是怎样
- That's not me! - What?
-那不是我！ -什么？
That's not you! Life is good again!
那不是你！美好的生命 又再度来临了！
Ride 'em, cowgirl!
骑上去，牛仔女！
That bastard taped over me!
那浑蛋录了别人在我的带子上！
Is that a problem?
那有什么问题吗？
It's just so insulting. Spring for a new blank tape, doctor!
真是太侮辱人了 花钱买新的空白带子嘛，医师！
Yes, but the important thing is that we have each other, right?
是的，但是重要的是我们拥有彼此 不是吗？
Well, yeah. It's just so rude!
嗯，是的，不过这非常没礼貌！
- And the way we did it was a lot better.. - Are you going to finish that sentence?
-我们做的方式要比那个好太多… -你要把这个句子说完吗？
I can't imagine what he sees in her.
我无法想像他在她身上 看到什么吸引人的
She actually makes me miss that pill-popping ex-wife of his.
她还真让我怀念起他那嗑药的前妻
Hello, dear.
哈，亲爱的
- What's going on? - We were just chitchatting.
-怎么了？ -我们只是在随便聊聊
- How's your friend? - A little better.
-你的朋友还好吗？ -有好一点了
Do you know who's moving back into town? Tom and Sue's daughter, Jen.
你知道谁要搬回城里了吗？ 汤姆跟苏的女儿，珍
You remember her, Michael. She's lovely, well-behaved and single.
你记得她的，麦克 她很可爱，行为举止端庄，而且单身
- I'm not interested. - Please, darling, let's be honest.
-我没有兴趣 -拜托，亲爱的，我们老实说
You can have all the sailor fun you want with that one.
你跟那个也可以享受像船员般的乐趣的
- But let's be real. - All right, stop.
-但是我们要面对现实 -好了，停
All Phoebe has done is try and get you to like her. Maybe it's not clear..
菲比所做的一切都是为了要让 你们喜欢她，或许不是很明显…
but she did her best.
但是她已经尽力而为了
- She's a little different than you are. - Michael, a pimp spit in her mouth.
-她是跟你们有点不同 -麦克，一个坏蛋吐口水在她嘴里
So what? If I can get past that, it shouldn't bother you.
那又如何？如果我都无所谓了 你们有什么好在乎的
You don't have to like her. Just accept the fact that I do.
你们没有必要去喜欢她 只需要接受我喜欢她的事实就可以
If you can't even be civil to the woman I love..
如果你们无法对我爱的女人…
- The woman you what? - Yeah, the woman you what?
-你什么的女人？ -是啊，你什么的女人？
The woman I love.
我爱的女人
I love you.
我爱你
Something I shouldn't say for the first time, in front of my parents..
我不该当我父母面前 第一次说这种话
and Tom and Sue.
还有汤姆跟苏面前
Who are, by the way, the most sinfully boring people I've ever met in my life.
对了，他们是我一生中 遇过最无聊的人
- I love you too. - You do?
-我也爱你 -真的？
How great is this?
很棒吗？
Wanna get out of here?
想要离开这里吗？
- Mom, Dad. Thanks for dinner. - I had a great time.
-爸妈，谢谢你们的晚餐 -我很开心
It was really top-drawer. And here's something rich.
这里真的很高级，而且更棒的是…
Thirteen bathrooms in this place, I threw up in the coat closet.
这里有十三间浴室 但是我吐在衣帽间里面
Ta-ta!
拜了！
One more time from the top!
从头再来一次！
Rachel, please! That is so inappropriate!
瑞秋，拜托！ 这实在太不恰当了！